<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction on Cloudneeti Docs</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Introduction on Cloudneeti Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png  should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png  Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent Go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in Go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using Go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Go to Hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your OS and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at Install Hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the Hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/configurationguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/configurationguide/</guid>
      <description>Configuration and User Guide Introduction : Cloudneeti is a governance cohort, bringing together an integrated approach across various disciplines of governance. With some simple configurations, Cloudneeti can help you pull information from applications / systems deployed on Azure and inform you through various notifications, dashboards and reports about –
 Compliance against industry standards such as PCI DSS 3.2, HIPAA, Cyber Security Foundations, Security Benchmark, NIST CSF, GDPR. Optimizing your Spend on the cloud subscription (are you over-subscribed or under-subscribed) Reliability of your cloud environments (efficacy of backups, downtime alerts) Reducing Risk by detecting and alerting non-compliant configurations  Types of User Roles  License Administrator - can do the following activities Subscription Administrator Subscription Reader      License Administrator Subscription Administrator Subscription Reader     View Dashboard :white_check_mark: :white_check_mark: :white_check_mark:   Add License Administrator :white_check_mark: :x: :x:   Add Tenant :white_check_mark: :x: :x:   Edit Tenant :white_check_mark: :x: :x:   Delete Tenant :white_check_mark: :x: :x:   Add Subscription :white_check_mark: :x: :x:   Edit Subscription :white_check_mark: :x: :x:   Delete Subscription :white_check_mark: :x: :x:   Configure Subscription :white_check_mark: :white_check_mark: :x:    Onboarding Azure Subscriptions to Cloudneeti To onboard an Azure subscription to your Cloudneeti product</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/installationguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/installationguide/</guid>
      <description>Vagus elidunt Mole et vultus populifer quaque primoque non Lorem markdownum pignora pelle est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de pectora summo. Redit teque digerit hominumque toris verebor lumina non cervice subde tollit usus habet Arctonque, furores quas nec ferunt. Quoque montibus nunc caluere tempus inhospita parcite confusaque translucet patri vestro qui optatis lumine cognoscere flos nubis! Fronde ipsamque patulos Dryopen deorum.
 Exierant elisi ambit vivere dedere Duce pollice Eris modo Spargitque ferrea quos palude  Rursus nulli murmur; hastile inridet ut ab gravi sententia!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/releasesummary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/releasesummary/</guid>
      <description>This page is hidden in menu Quondam non pater est dignior ille Eurotas Latent te facies Lorem markdownum arma ignoscas vocavit quoque ille texit mandata mentis ultimus, frementes, qui in vel. Hippotades Peleus pennas conscia cuiquam Caeneus quas.
 Pater demittere evincitque reddunt Maxime adhuc pressit huc Danaas quid freta Soror ego Luctus linguam saxa ultroque prior Tatiumque inquit Saepe liquitur subita superata dederat Anius sudor  Cum honorum Latona O fallor in sustinui iussorum equidem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/troubleshooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/troubleshooting/</guid>
      <description>Ubi loqui Mentem genus facietque salire tempus bracchia Lorem markdownum partu paterno Achillem. Habent amne generosi aderant ad pellem nec erat sustinet merces columque haec et, dixit minus nutrit accipiam subibis subdidit. Temeraria servatum agros qui sed fulva facta. Primum ultima, dedit, suo quisque linguae medentes fixo: tum petis.
Rapit vocant si hunc siste adspice Ora precari Patraeque Neptunia, dixit Danae Cithaeron armaque maxima in nati Coniugis templis fluidove. Effugit usus nec ingreditur agmen ac manus conlato.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation &amp; Deployment Guide</title>
      <link>http://example.org/docs/gettingstarted/gettingstartedmarketplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/docs/gettingstarted/gettingstartedmarketplace/</guid>
      <description>Getting Started with Cloudneeti VM for Azure Marketplace This article describes how to Automate Governance, Compliance, Reliability and Risk Monitoring for an enterprise using Azure
To deploy Cloudneeti VM from the Azure Marketplace:
Note: User logging into Azure Portal must have Global admin role to make the necessary configuration changes.
Purchase Cloudneeti from Azure Marketplace  Log in to the Microsoft Azure portal. Click Marketplace or click Browse &amp;gt; in the left side navigation, and select Marketplace from the list.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>